Julian Teofilov UI Developer

- +359 888 971167
- julian.teofilov@gmail.com
- Sofia, Bulgaria

- julian-teofilov.vercel.app
- github.com/barrelrolla
- in linkedin.com/in/julian-teofilov



9

Skills

User Interface
Web applications
Code optimization
Debugging
TypeScript

Profile

I'm a UI developer with 8 years of experience. I'm specialized both in front-end web development and video games. I have a diverse skillset of working with different programming languages, frameworks and game engines, such as C++, C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Phaser, Unity 3D and multiple proprietary game engines. Ability to work not only in a small team, but also with in a big international team creating AAA games such as The Division 2 and multiple Assassin's Creed titles.



React

Professional Experience

May 2018 - present

Ubisoft

UI Programmer

As a UI Programmer in Ubisoft, I have worked on multiple AAA video games, such as The Division 2, Assassin's Creed Valhalla: Dawn of Ragnarok, Assassin's Creed Mirage and Assassin's Creed Shadows. I have developed different HUD elements and menu pages in the game, and maintained others. In The Division 2 I was responsible for the in-game currency store while in Assassin's Creed I have worked on many HUD elements in different projects, as well as several menu pages. I have used tools like Jira, Confluence, Perfoce and many others to help with organizing tasks, documentation and source control.

Every project I have worked on comes with it's own set of challenges, but I am experienced in optimizing and debugging code, finding issues and delivering projects with a tight deadline.

Apr 2017 - Apr 2018

Melontech

JavaScript Programmer

As a front-end developer I have worked on several different projects, a web-based game using Phaser and TypeScript, a couple front-end web applications, one using Angular and the other using React, creating reusable components as well as creating libraries for use on other projects.

Every project I have worked on during my time there used a different framework and a different variation of JavaScript. I have proven my ability to learn new technologies and adapt fast.

I have used REST APIs, unit tests as well as tools like Jira, webpack, Git and many others to help with the development process.

Mar 2012 - Mar 2018

Ubisoft

Development Tester

As a Development Tester I worked on projects from their very beginning. I had to provide feedback on design documents and later test and give feedback on features. Securing working builds for reviews and milestones was also a huge part of the job. As I was one of the first development testers in the studio and we had a lot of build stability issues at the time, I helped a lot in creating a workflow that would allow us to have stable builds and integrate changes without major issues.

Education

2016 – 2017 **Telerik Academy**

Software Engineer

In this one-year course I learned programming basics using C#; web development, both front-end using JavaScript, and back-end using node.js; mobile applications for iOS and Android; and working with data bases. I graduated with one of the best results during my year.

2010 - 2014 IBS Botevgrad

International economic relations